<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Food | Allen.Han]]></title>
  <link href="http://allenhan.com/blog/categories/food/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://allenhan.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-09-20T16:21:28+12:00</updated>
  <id>http://allenhan.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Allen Han]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[About Coffee]]></title>
    <link href="http://allenhan.com/blog/about-coffee/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-20T16:02:18+12:00</updated>
    <id>http://allenhan.com/blog/about-coffee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Coffee is a popular drink, probably the most popular drink in the western world. I have been drinking coffee since, around 2003. Not a very big fan at first, because of the bitterness and the weird soureness in it. It was a pretty big cup of Cappaccino. I had a hard time to finish it off, with three packs of sugar and some milk, I swallowed the last drop of it. LOL, sounds like I suffered a lot with my first cup of real coffee.</p>

<p>After that, I haven&rsquo;t touch anything with coffee on it for a while, but then I started my first job in Wellington, all the collegues there are coffee addicts. I was thinking, if they get so additive to coffee, there must be something good about this drinking. Then I wondered down to the coffee shop called Mojo on Willis St, I decided not to go too hard, and ordered a cup of Mocha. After a few minutes the friendly barista handed me the first coffee that I ever love. Instead of the weird bitterness and sourenss, I tates this lovely coffee aroma, and sweetness of chocolate, and I can also taste the milk too. From then on I fell in love with coffee.</p>

<p>All these years has passed by, I am drinking coffee on a regular basis now, I was keeping my self clear of additions. I am working on High st, with about 20 coffee shops in one kilometer radius. I have been trying all the different coffee from all these shops. The thing I kinda discovered is, usually big coffee franchaises, (i.e. Starbucks) are pretty bad at making coffee, but the small shops even coffee carts makes better coffee. Making coffee is pretty much the same as making everything else, even the slightest mistake will ruin the whole cup. One&rsquo;s concentration is the most important thing.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
